

Malik Amir Hamza Khan

Contact

Address

E10/4 Iskanderabad, District Mianwali, Punjab

Phone

+923000688951

Email

malikameerhamza2010@gmail.com

Additional Skills

- · Node.js
- Angular
- ElectronJS
- Ionic
- PHP
- React Native
- React
- Java
- Mongodb
- Database Designing
- Software QA Testing
- Adobe XD

Professional Summary

Experienced Full Stack Developer with 3 years in the industry and highlevel proficiency in the following programs: JavaScript Technologies,Web Development, Native App Development expertise with HTML and CSS seeks to establish a career as the Full Stack Developer for Renaissance Tech Developers. I am very familiar and experienced with Web Application Architecture and have worked with a good number of successful development teams.

Work Experience

11/2016 - Present

Freelancer.com/Upwork.com

Full Stack Developer,

Finish Projects related to Nodejs, Angular, Ionic, Test Cases, ElectronJS, PHP, Adobe XD, Database Designing

02-2017 - 02-2020

Bumper Barrier - New York, USA

Full Stack Developer,

Expertise in Web/Desktop development using Node.js, ElectronJS, Angular, Mongodb.

Unit Tests and Integrations Tests using Jest and End to End Testing (E2E) using Puppeteer also frameworks Mocha and Chai and Appium.

Coding, Compiling, Unit testing, integration, packaging and deployment of developed software

Work with an established team of developers and interact with product managers,

marketing teams and designers. Provides technical advice and assists in solving programming problems. Strong working knowledge of development techniques and methodologies. Makes recommendations towards the development of new code or to reuse of existing code.

Makes recommendations towards the development of new code or reuse of existing code Knowledge of modern web development frameworks and tools.

Assists in preparing project plans using project management tools

02-2020 - Present

Hypertext Solutions Pvt. Limited - Islamabad, Pakistan

Full Stack Developer,

Expertise in Web/Desktop development using Node.js, ElectronJS, Angular, Mongodb.

Unit Tests and Integrations Tests using Jest and End to End Testing (E2E) using Puppeteer also frameworks

Mocha and Chai and Appium.

Education

November-2014 - December-2018

COMSATS University Islamabad, Abbottabad Campus

Bachelor of Computer Science, Graduated with 3.32 GPA